残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になる
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で 運命さえまだ知らない 痛い気な瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使のてて 窓辺からやがて取り立つ
ほとばしる 熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
次回予告
circuits power supply connected beginning system activation activation
voltage approaching critical level 0.5 0.2 rising initiate activation system
phase two synapses inserted nerve junctions connecting cardiograph
transmitting all circuits are operational no problems with initial
contact power supply to brachial muscles in the right of left arms all nerve
links check out normal checklist is satisfactory up to 2550 clear to 2580
prepare for third stage connection counting down to absolute borderline
0.9 0.7 0.5 0.4 0.3 something's going wrong in the third stage rejection
occurring in the nerve center elements break off contact cut circuit links
number one through number six negative the signals not being received
unit zero is out of control abort the experiment cut off the power supply
the experiment. Cut off the power supply.
Yes, sir!
Unit Zero has switched to standby power.
We've got 35 seconds before it comes to a complete stop.
It's gone for Cirque! Stay back!
Auto ejection system has been activated.
Damn it!
Complete shutdown.
Start the bottom line suppression system!
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
One, two, one, two!
puta!
Ray!
I see.
Ray Ayanami, age 14.
The first of the test subjects chosen in accordance with the Marduk report.
The first child.
Designated pilot for the Evangelion Unit Zero.
Her past has been eradicated.
All of her personal records have been erased.
So, do we have any idea what caused that incident during the last test?
We still don't know.
However, we believe that mental instability on the part of the pilot was a primary factor.
Mental instability? In Ray?
Yes.
Her mind became much more disturbed than we had anticipated.
So what did happen?
I don't know.
But she could have...
Did something occur to you?
No.
It can't be that.
The demolition of block B3 has been completed.
All technical department personnel must submit their data to the analysis group.
So, this is what the enemy looks like up close.
Magnificent!
Everything except the core has been left intact.
This is an almost perfect sample.
Thanks!
This will be a great help!
Okay.
So, have you found anything new yet?
What's that mean?
That's our system's code number for cannot be analyzed.
You mean you have no idea what this is?
Yeah.
What we do know is that the Angel is composed of a type of matter characterized by both particulate and waveform properties.
But you've at least found its power source, right?
Something like that.
But we haven't been able to figure out how it operates at all.
So we finally found something outside our experience.
It's a whole new world of mysteries.
For example, take a look at this.
This is the Angel's inherent waveform pattern.
Oh!
What about it?
It can't be.
Yes!
Although composed of a different form of matter, their actual composition in terms of the arrangement and coordinates of the pattern is a 99.85 animation.
That's our system.
Something like that.
But we haven't been able to figure out how it operates at all.
So we finally found something outside our experience.
It's a whole new world of mysteries.
For example, take a look at this.
This is the Angel's inherent waveform pattern.
Oh!
What about it?
It can't be.
Yes.
Although composed of a different form of matter, their actual composition in terms of the arrangement and coordinates of the pattern is a 99.85.
The order of this is the Angel is the direction.
The direction you can't be.
This is the is the glow, some of the conceituses.
the arrangement and coordinates of the pattern
is a 99.89% match to ours.
99.89%?
Yes, once again, we must acknowledge
how limited our level of understanding really is.
This is the core sample.
What about the rest of it?
There's not much left of it.
I don't think we can use it as a reference.
That's not a problem.
Dispose of the rest of it.
Yes, sir!
What's wrong?
Well, nothing.
Shinji, are you aware that when you say nothing
in that tone of voice, you might as well be shouting
for us to pay attention to you?
Nothing draws attention like evasive actions.
Well, it's just that my father seems to have burned his hands.
Burned them?
I was just wondering how it happened.
I'm not sure.
Do you know?
It was before you joined us.
Unit Zero went berserk during the activation trials.
You've heard about that.
Yeah?
It was bad.
The pilot was trapped inside the Eva.
Rei Ayanami.
Was she the pilot?
Yes.
And it was Commander Ikari who rescued her.
He opened the superheated hatch with his bare hands.
Bullshit.
My father did that?
Yes, he really did.
That's how he burned his hands.
Hey!
Over here!
Look at us!
No way!
No way out there, man!
I thought you were there!
Oh, my God.
Those guys are looking at us!
Yeah, they've all got such incredible breaths.
Uh-huh.
Hey, Big Shot, what are you staring at so intently?
Uh, nothing.
Who?
He's oldling Ray.
I am not.
Ah, come on.
We saw you lurking.
Yeah, Ray's mammaries.
Ray's silky thighs.
Yeah.
Her calves.
Her naughty bits.
Uh, look, it's nothing like that.
Then just what were you looking at?
You can't fool us, Shinji.
Mmm.
I was just wondering why she's always alone.
Huh?
Uh, come to think of it, she hasn't had any friends since she started here in the seventh grade.
There's just something about her that makes her hard to talk to.
Like she's in her own world.
She's probably just got a lousy personality.
You two are both Ava pilots, right?
You ought to know her better than any of us, Shinji.
Know what I mean?
Yeah, that's right.
I suppose.
But we don't talk.
Ava unit one is now entering the third stage cooling process.
Lower all systems phase three and cage six.
The harmonics and synchronization test results were good.
All numerical conditions have been satisfied.
Roger.
Transmit the results to Balthazar.
Transmitting the full range of the entry plug's personal data files to Melchior.
Data transmitting.
This is Melchior.
Roger.
Circuits connected.
Initiating third stage cooling process.
CBL circulation has begun.
Vent liquid waste to second purification system.
T minus one thousand 50 minutes until the Unit Zero reactivation experiment.
What is this stuff?
It's curry.
You mean you're still eating this instant junk?
Oh my god.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Look, you're a guest, so you've got no right to complain.
Misato, don't you want any?
Oh, sorry about that. Ta-da!
Slot some of that stuff on top of this stuff.
You can't be serious.
Go on! It's yummy to the max.
Okay.
Ordinary curry-flavored instant ramen can't be this good.
Yeah! Come on, let's eat.
Dig in, guys.
The trick is to put less hot water in the soup
so it forms the sludge.
Misato cooked, right?
You can tell?
Of course!
Who else could make instant soup taste so awful?
Next time you invite me over,
make sure it's Shinji's turn to cook.
You know, Shinji, you really ought to consider moving out.
You shouldn't let one bad roommate ruin your entire life, you know.
But I'm used to it now.
He's right, Ritsuko.
Never underestimate the ability of the human animal to adapt to its environment, right?
And anyway, if he doesn't move...
Oh.
Shinji, can I have another?
Right.
He's gonna have to go through an awful lot of trouble in red tape.
He just got his permanent security card, you know.
Oh!
I almost forgot again!
Shinji, I need a favor.
Ah, here it is.
What is it?
This is Rei's new security card.
I keep forgetting to give this to her.
Would you mind delivering this to her before you go into headquarters?
Uh, sure.
Hmm.
What's the matter?
You're staring at Rei's picture, aren't you?
Ah!
I'm not!
Oh, yes you are, Shinji.
Yeah, I was not!
I think I embarrassed him.
Now you've got an excuse to go over to Rei's place, don't you?
Stop teasing me!
But I love teasing you, you go so ballistic.
Just like Misato.
No!
I just find it strange that I know so little about her, even though we're both Eva pilots.
She's a nice girl, but she's like your father.
She's not very adept at...
She's not very adept at what?
Living, I guess.
She will disappear.
Because I'm not proving that I'm going to waste my family so happy that you can try it again.
Hello there!
I'm sorry for intruding.
It's me, Shinji Ikari.
I'm coming in, okay?
Hmm.
These can't be rays.
Come on.
Um, Ray, I...
I didn't mean...
Oh!
Oh, yes!
Well, you get off.
Will you get off?
Uh, well, I was asked to, uh, well, I was asked to, uh, you know, so I, uh, what was
it?
Uh, the card, your card, uh, it's been, uh, renewed.
Uh, so I was asked to deliver it.
I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
Ritsuko said she forgot to give it to you.
It's true.
I rang your bell, but there was no reply, and the door was unlocked, so I, um...
Uh-huh.
Central Dogma is currently open to the public.
Group three should proceed to direct gate four.
Uh, here.
This is your new card.
Ritsuko told me to deliver this to you?
Look, I'm sorry.
About what?
Um, uh, well, um, um, aren't you going to have a reactivation test today?
Aren't you scared, Ray?
Aren't you afraid of piloting unit zero?
Why?
Well, I heard that you were hurt pretty bad in an earlier experiment, so I thought you
might be...
Aren't you Commander Ikari's son?
Mm-hmm.
Don't you have faith in your own father's work?
No, of course not!
How could I ever trust him again?
What's wrong?
Ray, are you alright?
It was bad.
The pilot was trapped inside the Ava.
And it was Commander Ikari who rescued her.
He opened the superheated hatch with his bare hands.
Ray, can you hear me?
Yes.
We will now begin the unit zero reactivation experiment.
Initiate primary connection.
Connect the main power supply.
Activation voltage has passed the critical point.
Roger.
Shift format to phase two.
Connecting pilot to unit zero.
Opening circuits.
Pulse and harmonics are normal.
No problems detected.
We are in sync.
All nerve links completed.
Central nerve system elements are nominal.
Recalculating.
No error corrections.
The checklist is satisfactory up to 2590.
Approaching critical mark.
2.5 more.
1.7.
1.2.
1.0.
0.8.
0.6.
0.5.
0.4.
0.3.
0.2.
0.1.
0.1 and rising.
Borderline clear.
Unit zero has been activated.
Roger.
Beginning interlock test.
Ikari, an unidentified object is rapidly approaching nerve central.
It may be the fifth angel.
Abort the test.
Place all operations on first stage alert.
You're not gonna use unit zero are you?
She's not ready to fight yet.
Unit one status.
It can be ready in 380 seconds.
Make it so.
Yes sir.
Ray, is ready?
I got cool.
Yes sir.
Rahit.
You got it.
He got it.
I got it.
You know I'm ready.
I'm ready.
You got it.
I got it.
I'm ready.
Go ahead!
I got it.
I am ready.
I'm ready.
Make it so.
Yes, sir.
Ray?
Reactivation has been successfully completed.
Return now.
The target is passing over Tonosawa.
Unit 1 is beginning launch sequence.
Releasing primary lock bolts.
Lock bolts released.
Roger.
Removing secondary restraint.
The target is now intruding into Lake Ashino airspace.
AVA, Unit 1 is ready for launch.
Launch AVA!
We're detecting a high-energy reaction inside the target.
What'd you say?
The energy torch is accelerating and massing upon itself.
It can't be.
Look out, Doc!
The sun.
Now, shoot him!
Fly me to the moon and let me play among the stars
Let me see what spring is like on Jupiter and Mars
Another moon, hold my hand
Another moon, darling, kiss me
Fill my heart with sun and let me sing forevermore
You are all I love for, all my words, I can adore
Another moon, please be true
Another moon, I love you
Shinji survives, but he's injured and begins to deteriorate badly
To the point where Rey is to take over in the next battle
As Misato desperately tries to pinpoint the angel's weak spot
The ultimate in heavy artillery is prepared to face the new menace
Will she succeed in time to save Rey?